[{"id": 2131, "question": "Bruce Jun Fan Lee was born in the hour of the Dragon, between 6 and 8 a.m., in the \"Year of the Dragon\" on November 27, 1940 at the Jackson Street Hospital in San Francisco's Chinatown. Today, a plaque in the hospital's entry remembers the place of his birth. Bruce's birth, in the hour and the year of Dragon, is a powerful symbol in Chinese astrology . It would be a strong indication of the powerful life that was to be lived by Bruce Lee and the explosive influence his life would have on countless others. At the age of three months, Lee Hoi Chuen, his wife Grace and baby Bruce returned to Hong Kong where Bruce would be raised until the age of 18. Probably because of the long ocean voyage and the change in climates, Bruce was not a strong child in his very early years, a condition that woul...\n\nQ: The plaque at the entrance of the Jackson Street Hospital is considered as   _  .", "options": ["an obvious sign of Bruce's powerful life", "a strong influence of Bruce's life on others", "a reminder of Bruce Lee's birthplace", "a powerful symbol in Chinese astrology"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3026, "question": "While elephants are respected by the people of Thailand, they are also used as beasts of burdens . Today, these majestic animals are extensively used to help carry wood for the logging industry. It is therefore nice to hear that on National Elephant Day the mighty mammals are treated like a king, and served with meals fit for a king. One of the biggest celebrations took place at the Pattaya Resort in Thailand's Chonburi Province. Fifty-two elephants, some wearing beautiful clothes, arrived bright and early for the big day. Each was first blessed with holy water by a professional elephant rider and then led to the grand feast, which served an unlimited supply of their favorite treats--bananas, dragon fruits , pineapples, assorted melons, apples and the list went on and on! The elephants ate...\n\nQ: The celebrations held at the Pattaya Resort aimed to   _  .", "options": ["show visitors the elephants' great performance", "honor elephants for their devotion to the country", "encourage people to play with elephants", "show visitors the beautiful scenery in Thailand"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1725, "question": "Money might not grow on trees, but scientists have confirmed that gold is found in the leaves of some plants. Researchers from Australia say that the presence of the particles in an eucalyptus tree's leaves indicates that deposits are buried many meters below. They believe that the discovery offers a new way to locate the valuable metal in difficult-to-reach locations. Dr. Mel Lintern from Australia's Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organization (CSIRO) said, \"We've found a lot of the easy deposits in Australia in this way. Now we are trying to find the more difficult ones that are buried tens of meters below. And the trees are providing us with a method to be able to do this.\" Using the Australian synchrotron - a vast machine that uses X-rays to explore matter in remarkabl...\n\nQ: We can infer that Dr. Lintern   _  .", "options": ["is not sure of the plant-analyzing method", "is very content with what he has achieved", "is tired of detecting gold deposits in the wild", "is confident of the plant-analyzing method"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1216, "question": "A number of times Rosemary edged closer to Gordon , meaning to take his arm, but he edged away from her. She thought that she had offended him deeply, and that he was disappointed because she had pushed him away. She would have apologized if he had given her half a chance. But as a matter of fact, he was scarcely thinking of this any longer. It was the money business that was troubling him now. And the fact was that he would soon have to confess it. What nonsense it made of all he had said! Presently she stopped him, and swung him round to face her. \"Gordon, why won't you speak to me?\" she said. \"Are you still angry with me for what happened just now?\" \"No, I was never angry with you. You're not to blame. Something else has been worrying me all the way along, I've only eight pence left. I ...\n\nQ: It is clear that Gordon had not intended to    _   .", "options": ["tell her he had a little money left", "accept any money from her", "blame her for making him angry", "have such an expensive dinner"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3400, "question": "One of the best-known American writers of children's books is Alfred Strong, or Doctor Strong, as he is better known to readers everywhere. Now, an art show called \"Doctor Strong From Then to Now\" is travelling around the United States. The pictures and drawings show the history of Doctor Strong. Doctor Strong first became famous almost fifty years ago when his first children's book was published. Since then, he has written forty-five books that have sold more than one hundred million copies around the world. Doctor Strong's books are known for their easy use of words and colorful, hand-drawn pictures. These drawings bring life to his imaginary creatures. The Cat in the Hat, Horton the Elephant, The Grinch Who Stole Christmas, and hundreds of others. The San Diego Museum, in California, or...\n\nQ: Alfred Strong is a famous   _   in the United States.", "options": ["doctor", "artist", "writer", "reader"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2619, "question": "In the dark and damp market,Chen ShuChu,near her sixties,owns a stall that her father left her.The stall,called YuanJin Vegetables,is her everything.Chen earns only a little money by selling vegetables,but she has donated about $321,550 to help poor children. In March,Forbes magazine named her one of the 48 great philanthropists from the AsiaPacific region.A month later,TIME magazine selected the year's top 100 influential people and Chen was one of them.Although she has received many honours and rewards,Chen only cares about her vegetable stall and whether her regular customers buy her vegetables or not.\"I do not place great importance on money.When I donate to help others,I feel happy and I can sleep well at night.\" Chen said. Chen's ability to donate such a great deal of money has led m...\n\nQ: Why has Chen been called \"market manager\"?", "options": ["Because she has received many honours and rewards.", "Because she often arrives early and leaves late in the market.", "Because she has donated much money to the market.", "Because her vegetable stall is the biggest one in the market."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2225, "question": "A Day of Design Sunday, June 27,2010 9 a. m. ~ 4 p. m. Thomas College Student Center Join us for a free day of fun! A Day of Design will encourage those interested in flowers and design to get in touch with their creative side and get some tips from the experts - Jeff and Scott. Pleas see the schedule below for details about this wonderful opportunity! 9:00 a.m. - 10:30 a.m. Registration for the day runs from 9 a.m. in the Student Center. Later guests will take a tour of the Thomas College campus before the day's events. 10:30 a. m. ~ 12:00 p. m. Jeff and Scott will design more than a dozen arrangements in a variety of sizes and colors and auction will be held and guests will have the opportunity to bid on the flower arrangements. 12:00 p. m. ~ 1:00 p. m. A delightful boxed lunch will be s...\n\nQ: What are guests supposed to do from 9:00 a. m. to 10:30 a. m.?", "options": ["To design flower arrangements.", "To enjoy a wine and cheese party.", "To learn how to create a centerpiece.", "To take a tour of the Thomas College campus."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2758, "question": "\"I would almost rather see you dead,\" Robert S. Cassatt, a leading banker of Philadelphia, shouted when his twenty-year-old eldest daughter announced that she wanted to become an artist. In the 19th century, playing at drawing or painting on dishes was all right for a young lady, but serious work in art was not. And when the young lady's family ranked among the best of Philadelphia's social families, such an idea could not even be considered. That was how Mary Cassatt, born in 1844, began her struggle as an artist. She did not tremble before her father's anger. Instead, she opposed him with courage and at last made him change his mind. Mary Cassatt gave up her social position and all thought of a husband and a family, which in those times was unthinkable for a young lady. In the end, after...\n\nQ: What made Mary Cassatt's \"struggle\" to become a recognized artist especially hard?", "options": ["Her father opposed her.", "She was a woman.", "She had no social position.", "She did not come from an artist's family."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 746, "question": "Viruses come in an enormous number of shapes and forms.As we begin to understand them more,the hope is we might be able to control them better, says Carl Zimmer.And who knows,the day might come when we can treat them as friends not enemies. Science writer Carl Zimmer says that in his utopia there would be a global public health system with sophisticated drugs and vaccines to deal with any virus that could cause us trouble. Viruses are by far the most abundant life form on Earth.If you took all the stars in the universe and multiplied that number by a million,that's how many viruses we think are on the planet. Zimmer thinks we should face the future with a mixture of optimism and preparing for the worse.He thinks we will face some unknown virus that will cause a lot of damage-history tells ...\n\nQ: The passage tells us   _", "options": ["scientists have made a medicine that can kill all kinds of viruses", "viruses have ever done great harm to us human beings", "universal anti-viral drug has existed for many years", "viruses are always our enemies"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1755, "question": "Having spent five years searching for her older brother, Miss Lund was unbelievable to think she had been working in the same building for five months. Mr.Philips, 33, and Miss Lund last saw each other almost twenty years ago after their father, also called Stephen, 56, lost contact with his son from a previous relationship.Miss Lund, only five at that time, moved to India with her father and mother Rose, while Steven lived with his mother in Wolverhapton. By the time Miss Lund and her parents returned to Leeds, the family had lost all contact with Mr.Philips.On turning 18, Lund started to track down her long-lost half brother, even asking customers at the shop where she worked.But despite checking on Internet sites such as Friends Reunited and MySpace, it wasn't until the pair started wor...\n\nQ: How long had the brother and sister been working in the same building before they got to know each other?", "options": ["5 years", "13 years", "20 years", "5 months"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1332, "question": "Jogging has become the most popular individual sport in America. Many theories,even some mystical ones,have been advanced to explain the popularity of jogging. The plain truth is that jogging is a cheap,quick and efficient way to maintain (or achieve) physical fitness. The most useful sort of exercise is exercise that develops the heart,lungs, and circulatory systems. If these systems are fit,the body is ready for almost any sport and for almost any sudden demand made by work or emergencies. One can train more specifically,as by developing strength for weight lifting or the ability to run straight ahead for short distances with great power as in football,but running trains your heart and lungs to deliver oxygen more efficiently to all parts of your body. It is worth doing that: this sort o...\n\nQ: The author^s attitude towards jogging is   _  ..", "options": ["doubtful", "critical", "approving", "objective"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1635, "question": "One day a student went to see his teacher. He had been given an important position and now was coming to say goodbye to his teacher. The old man asked him how he would live among high officials. The student answered, \" I will be all right. I have prepared a hundred high hats, one for each official I will meet. I am sure I will succeed.\" The teacher got angry on hearing this. \"What?\" he cried. \"Is this what ten years of my teaching has made of you? Nothing but flatterer ?\" \"Excuse me, honored master,\" the student rose to his feet and apologized hurriedly. \"But you have always been absorbed in your studies and don't know how vulgar the world has come to be. There are few men in the world who are above flatterers like you.\" \"There is something true in what you said,\" the teacher nodded, smili...\n\nQ: The student would live among high officials by  _  .", "options": ["selling hats to them", "making a hundred hats for them", "flattering them", "serving them"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3203, "question": "At an airport I overheard a father and a daughter in their last moments together. They had announced her plane's departure. Standing near the door, he said to his daughter: \"I love you. I wish you enough.\" \"Daddy, our life together has been more than enough. Your love is all I ever needed. I wish you enough too, Daddy.\" They kissed goodbye and she left. He walked over toward the window where I was seated. I tried not to _ his privacy, but he welcomed me in by asking: \"Did you ever say goodbye to someone knowing it would be forever?\" \"Yes, I have,\" I replied. \"Forgive me for asking, but why is this a forever goodbye?\" I asked. \"I am old and she lives much too far away. I have challenges ahead and the reality is that her next trip back will be for my funeral. \" \"When you were saying goodbye ...\n\nQ: The author began his talk with the old man  _  .", "options": ["when he stood by the window", "because the old man wanted to", "because he was interested in how to say to say goodbye", "when he sat around thinking about saying goodbye."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2955, "question": "The southwest of Australia has been named as one of 25\"hot spots\" for future species extinction because of global warming.A new study says global warming will become a top cause of extinction across the world,with thousands of species of plantsand animals likely to be wiped out in the coming decades. According to the study,global warming ranks among the most serious threats to the planet's biodiversity and,under some conditions,may be more than that due to deforestation.This study provides even stronger scientific evidence that global warming will result in catastrophic species losses across the planet.Last month,a UN study said humans were responsible for the worst extinction and urged extra efforts to reach a UN target of slowing the rate of losses by 2010. Scientists disagree about how ...\n\nQ: We can infer if the climate warms,the animals in Australia will most probably move to the   _   .", "options": ["north", "east", "west", "south"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1438, "question": "I'm usually fairly skeptical about any research that concludes that people are either happier or unhappier or more or less certain of themselves than they were 50 years ago. While any of these statements might be true, they are practically impossible to prove scientifically. Still, I was struck by a report which concluded that today's children are significantly more anxious than children in the 1950s. In fact, the analysis showed, normal children aged 9 to 17 exhibit a higher level of anxiety today than children who were treated for mental illness 50 years ago. Why are America's kids so stressed? The report cites two main causes: increasing physical isolation brought on by high divorce rates and less involvement in community, among other things and a growing perception that the world is a ...\n\nQ: According to the analysis, compared with normal children today, children treated as mentally ill 50 years ago   _  .", "options": ["probably suffered less from anxiety", "were considered less individualistic", "were less isolated physically", "were probably less selfcentered"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2737, "question": "We experience different forms of the Sun's energy every day. We can see its light and feel its warmth. The Sun is the major source of energy for our planet. It causes the evaporation of water from the oceans and lakes. Sunlight also provides the energy used by green plants to make their own food. These green plants then provide food for all organisms on the Earth. Much of the energy that comes from the Sun never reaches the Earth's surface. It is either reflected or absorbed by the gases in the upper atmosphere. Of the energy that reaches the lower atmosphere,30% is reflected by clouds or the Earth's surface. The remaining 70% warms the surface of the planet, causes water to evaporate, and provides energy for the water cycle and weather. Only a tiny part, approximately 0.023%, is actually ...\n\nQ: We learn from the passage that  _  .", "options": ["all living things on the Earth depend on the Sun for their food", "a forest looks dark in winter because it absorbs solar energy", "only 0.023% of the energy from the Sun is made use of on the Earth", "greenhouse gases allow heat energy to escape from the Earth's surface"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2027, "question": "Vancouver. B.C.--For six months. Ted Schredd and Deanna Kopel cycled around North America to show others a way to help the environment. \"Nobody wants to breathe dirty air--but for the air to change. People have to stop driving cars,\" says Ted, \"If more people start riding bikes, the air will be cleaner.\" Ted started his trip alone. He had $160 in his pocket and plans to cycle around North America. He left his hometown of Vancouver, and when he arrived in San Diego he got the chance to make some extra money for the rest of his 13, 000 km trip. A cyclist he met asked him to speak at an environment meeting in Texas. Within a few hours, Ted was on a plane to the meeting and a big surprise. When he met Deanna at the meeting, they talked for six hours straight. It was love at first sight. The ne...\n\nQ: What difficulty did Deanna meet after starting the trip with Ted?", "options": ["Getting free meals in restaurant.", "Sleeping in people's yards.", "Getting up very early.", "Missing her friends."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1113, "question": "If you wish to dance with a certain lady, go to her, bow, and say, \"May I have the pleasure of a dance?\" If it is a formal dance with programs, she will tell you which dance she will have with you; if there are no programs, she will either rise and dance with you, or she may say, \"I have this dance taken.\" Or she may say, \"I am sorry, I am not dancing this dance.\" This may be a polite way of saying that she does not want to dance with you, or it may be that she is tired and wants to rest; you will have to judge which is her attitude. Do not expect a lady whom you have invited to dance in advance for a dance to make any attempt to find you. It is her part to remain seated until you find her. Bow and say, \"I believe this is my dance.\" At the end of a dance, thank your partner, but do not lea...\n\nQ: When a lady says, \"I am sorry I am not dancing this dance.\", she actually means  _  .", "options": ["she is not willing to dance with you", "she is too tired to dance with you", "she is not good at dancing at all", "either A or B"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3426, "question": "Discover Newsmagazine of science devoted to the wonders and stories of modern science, written for the educated general reader. Published by Disney Magazine Publishing Co., Discover tells many of the same stories professionals read in Scientific American. A truly delightful family science magazine, each issue brings to light new and newsworthy topics to make dinnertime and water-cooler conversations interesting. Cover Price: $59.88 Price: $19.95 ($1.66/issue) You Save: $39.93 (67%) Issues: 12 issues/12 months Self Published by Conde Nast Publications Inc., Self is a handbook devoted to women's overall physical and mental health. Every issue contains usable articles such as \"Style Lab\", in which wearable clothes are mixed and matched on non-models and the \"Eat-right Road Map\", with tips on ...\n\nQ: Those who are interested in management and the use of high technology would probably choose  _  .", "options": ["In Style.", "Self.", "Wired.", "Discover."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 944, "question": "It was near dusk, and Kim Cooper and her husband, Steve, were trucking through northern Kentucky transportation auto parts from Louisville to Detroit for a goods company. \"Steve, wake up!\" she shouted. \"There's a truck on fire!\" Inside the burning truck, Ronnie Sanders, 38, was fighting for his life. He'd been running a heavy load of tractors and forklifts from Georgia to Indianapolis when a van in front of him stopped suddenly in traffic on the icy road. As Ronnie bore down, he could see children in the backseat. The truck's bulk would probably protect him from the worst of the impact, but the force of 23 tons would likely crush everyone inside the van. \"I figured instead of killing other people, I'd just put the truck in the ditch.\" At the bottom, rocks cut a fuel tank, which caught fire...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be the best title of this passage?", "options": ["Heroes: The Coopers", "Heroes: Roadside Flames", "Accidents on the Icy Road", "Accidents in the Ditch"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3430, "question": "I was at a busy traffic crossing waiting to cross to the other side. There was a family--a man, his wife and an old lady, waiting to cross with me. Then, the light turned green and all of us walked quickly across the road. The light lasted very short, and changed into red in no time. I noticed that both the man and his wife had crossed along with me and the old lady was left behind. I quickly realized what happened. When the light turned dreen again, I ran over to the other side, offered the old lady my right hand and we quickly walked together to the other side of the road. I used my left hand to stop any oncoming traffic so that even if the crossing signal turned red, we cuold make it to the other side safely. In the meantime, both the man and his wife realized that they had left the old...\n\nQ: What does the auther learn from his experiece ?", "options": ["Being kind to others can mean a lot.", "One should take care of his parents.", "Old people are afraid of traffic.", "Strangers can be helpful to others."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2604, "question": "Eighteen-year-old Dana Kiger is happily running after balls on the soccer field. But not long ago, she couldn't remember her love of the game, her parents' faces or even her name. At 16, the Tennessee honor student and star athlete was hit from behind while playing in a soccer game. She fell to the ground, her head striking the hard ground. The blow knocked out nearly all of Kiger's memories. With no physical injury or unusual change in her brain, doctors thought Kiger's memory would return in a few days. But it did not. And two and a half years later, it still hasn't. Kiger--who has no memory of her family, her childhood or her life before her injury--has had to create new memories, restart relationships and relearn old skills. \"The only thing I had ...I could walk, write, but I didn't kn...\n\nQ: According to the text, which of the following is TRUE of Kiger?", "options": ["Now she appears on the soccer field again.", "She has recovered from her physical injury.", "At age 16, she began showing interest in soccer.", "She will explore her past memories in college."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 341, "question": "John Blanchard stood up from the bench, straightened his Army uniform, and studied the crowd of people making their way through Grand Central Station. He looked for the girl whose heart he knew, but whose face he didn't, the girl with the rose. His interest in her had begun thirteen months before in a Florida library. Taking a book off the shelf he found himself intrigued, not with the words of the book, but with the notes penciled in the margin. The soft handwriting reflected a thoughtful soul and insightful mind. In the front of the book, he discovered the previous owner's name, Miss Hollis Maynell. With time and effort he located her address. She lived in New York City. He wrote her a letter introducing himself and inviting her to correspond. The next day he was shipped overseas for ser...\n\nQ: What was the real Miss Hollis Maynell like?", "options": ["She was a plump woman with graying hair.", "She was a slightly fat girl, with blonde hair.", "She was a middle - aged woman in her forties.", "She was a young, pretty girl wearing a green suit."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2428, "question": "Learning a Second Language Some people learn a second language easily. Other people have trouble learning a new language. How can you help yourself learn a new language, such as English? There are several ways to make learning English a little easier and more interesting. The first step is to feel confident about learning English. If you believe that you can learn, you will learn. Be patient. You don't have to understand everything all at once. It is natural to make mistakes when you learn something new. We can learn from our mistakes. The second step is to practise your English. For example,write in a diary every day. You will get used to writing in English,and you will feel comfortable expressing your ideas in English. After several weeks, you will see that your writing is improving. Bes...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of this passage?", "options": ["It is very important to learn a second language.", "Some people learn a second language easily while other people do not.", "There are ways to help you learn a second language more easily.", "Don't worry about making mistakes when learning a second language."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 903, "question": "When Charles Strattion was five, he stopped growing. His mother took him to see the famous showman, P. T. Barnum, and thought a small person would be the perfect addition to his show. He hired Charles' parents along with him, and they traveled around the world together. He gave the two-foot-tall Charles a new name, general Tom Thumb. He taught Tom how to sing, dance, act, and tell jokes. When he felt Tom was ready to perform on stage, he made up ads. To stir up great interest, he said that Tom was eleven years old and had come from England. Tom's act was very popular and brought in a lot of money. By the time Tom was an adult, he had grown very rich. He had become a billionaire at the age of twenty-five. Fortunately for Tom, Mr. Barnum added more little people to his show, and Tom became l...\n\nQ: What does the author think about Tom Thumb's wedding?", "options": ["People gave it too much of their attention.", "It helped people cheer up in a dark time", "It was funny and ridiculous", "Tom and Lavinia were stupid."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1636, "question": "One day a student went to see his teacher. He had been given an important position and now was coming to say goodbye to his teacher. The old man asked him how he would live among high officials. The student answered, \" I will be all right. I have prepared a hundred high hats, one for each official I will meet. I am sure I will succeed.\" The teacher got angry on hearing this. \"What?\" he cried. \"Is this what ten years of my teaching has made of you? Nothing but flatterer ?\" \"Excuse me, honored master,\" the student rose to his feet and apologized hurriedly. \"But you have always been absorbed in your studies and don't know how vulgar the world has come to be. There are few men in the world who are above flatterers like you.\" \"There is something true in what you said,\" the teacher nodded, smili...\n\nQ: The teacher was angry with  _  .", "options": ["himself", "the society", "his student", "high officials"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1178, "question": "Scientists have exactly discovered the set of brain cells involved in making risky decisions, and have been able to control them in rats using targeted light. By changing the activity of the cells they were able to change the behaviour of risk-taking rats to avoid risk, hinting the approach could in future be used to treat people with impulse control problems. Risk-taking is a key part of survival, knowing when to take a chance could pay off--such as moving to a new area to look for food when pickings are slim. While all animals need an element of risk, the preference towards it varies between individuals. Researchers found this variation, which determines how risk-averse an individual is, is regulated by brain cells in a region of the brain called the nucleus accumbens. This cluster of ne...\n\nQ: From the experiment with rats, we can conclude that   _  .", "options": ["the lack of DR2 cells results in a safe option", "the levels of DR2 have little to do with their choices", "the high levels of DR2 can make animals avoid risks", "the risky choice is a less rewarding option"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1787, "question": "Here is some must-know information from a handbook on how people behave in doing business in some countries. In Brazil Brazilians are warm and friendly.They often stand close when talking and it is common for them to touch the person on the shoulder.People often greet each other (particularly women)with light cheek kisses . Schedules tend to be flexible,with business meetings sometimes starting later than planned.But to be safe,be on time.Meals can stretch for hours--there's no such thing as rushing a meal in Brazil.Lunches also can start in the mid to late afternoon.Brazilians are social,preferring face-to-face communication over emails or phone calls. In Singapore Singaporeans shake hands when they meet and often also greet each other with a small,polite bow.Business cards should be offe...\n\nQ: In the UAE, when should you refuse the coffee if it is offered?", "options": ["When greeting seniors.", "When meeting the host alone.", "When attending a presentation.", "Whendining with business partners."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 524, "question": "Runners in a relay race pass a stick in one direction. However, merchants passed silk, gold, fruit, and glass along the Silk Road in more than one direction. They earned their living by traveling the famous Silk Road. The Silk Road was not a simple trading network. It passed through thousands of citied and towns. It started from eastern China, across Central Asia and the Middle East, and ended in the Mediterranean Sea. It was used from about 200 B, C, to about A, D, 1300, when sea travel offered new routes , It was sometimes called the world's longest highway. However, the Silk Road was made up of many routes, not one smooth path. They passed through what are now 18 countries. The routes crossed mountains and deserts and had many dangers of hot sun, deep snow and even battles. Only experie...\n\nQ: The Silk Road became less important because  _  .", "options": ["it was made up of different routes", "silk trading became less popular", "sea travel provided easier routes", "people needed fewer foreign goods"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1698, "question": "When 15-year-old Louisa Ball takes a nap, she sleeps for days on end, and no amount of shaking can fully wake her up. The British girl has a rare condition called Sleeping Beauty Sickness. Doctors don't know what causes it or how to cure it --only know that it strikes teenagers and goes away by itself after eight to 12 years. Louisa's mum, Lottie, told NBC News that the girl had flulike symptoms just over a year ago. Shortly afterward, she had her first period of long sleeping. She was eventually diagnosed with Kleine-Levin Syndrome, whose victims worldwide may number no more than 1,000. The victims live normally for weeks or months at a time, with normal sleep patterns and normal energy levels. Then, with little warning, they'll go to sleep for days or weeks at a time. So far, Louisa's lo...\n\nQ: Which is TRUE about Kleine-Levin Syndrome according to the passage?", "options": ["The victims usually sleep for days or weeks at a time.", "There are usually many warning signs before it attacks the victims.", "The victims are usually tired and in a bad mood.", "There are more than 1, 000 victims in the world."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1987, "question": "Shakespeare's Sister Let us imagine, since facts are so hard to come by, what would have happened had Shakespeare had a wonderfully gifted sister, called Judith. Shakespeare himself went, very probably -- his mother was an heiress -- to the grammar school, where he may have learnt Latin -- Ovid, Virgil and Horace -- and the elements of grammar and logic. He was, it is well known, a wild boy who poached rabbits, perhaps shot a deer, and had, rather sooner than he should have done, to marry a woman in the neighborhood, who bore him a child rather quicker than was right. That escapade sent him to seek his fortune in London. He had, it seemed, a taste for the theatre; he began by holding horses at the stage door. Very soon he got work in the theatre, became a successful actor, and lived at the...\n\nQ: From the passage, we can safely draw the conclusion that in the age of Shakespeare   _  .", "options": ["women couldn't possibly act on the stage or write plays", "women could enjoy themselves domestically and socially", "women couldn't make their achievements at any level", "women could make their own decision as to their marriage"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1021, "question": "A group of graduates, well established in their careers, were talking at a reunion and decided to visit their old university professor, now retired. During their visit, the conversation turned to complaints about stress in their work and lives. Offering his guests hot chocolate, the professor went into the kitchen and returned with a large pot of hot chocolate and other things including cups-porcelain , glass, crystal, some plain looking, some expensive, some elegant -- telling them to help themselves to the hot chocolate. When they all had a cup of hot chocolate in hand, the professor said: \"I notice that all the nice looking and expensive cups were taken, leaving behind the plain and cheap ones. While it is normal for you to want only the best for yourselves, that is the source of your p...\n\nQ: What is the purpose of the professor's words?", "options": ["To tell them life is not easy, so try their best to be happy.", "To educate them that the happiest people don't have the best of everything.", "To wish them to be grateful to their life and make the best of everything that they have.", "To use different cups to tell them they should try different things in life."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1003, "question": "Zoe Chambers was a successful PR(Public Relations) consultant and life was going well -- she had a great job, beautiful flat and a busy social life in London. Then one evening in June last year, she received a text message telling her she was out of work. \"The first two weeks were the most difficult to live through.\" she said. \"After everything I'd done for the company, they dismissed me by text! I was so angry and I just didn't feel like looking for another job. I hate everything about the city and my life.\" Then, Zoe received an invitation from an old school friend, Kathy, to come and stay. Kathy and her husband, Huw, had just bought a farm in north-west Wales. Zoe jumped at the chance to spend a weekend away from London, and now, ten months later she is still on the farm. \"The moment I ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is closest to the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["A friend in need is a friend indeed.", "Where there is a will, there is a way.", "A misfortune may turn out a blessing.", "Kill two birds with one stone."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1187, "question": "Why do men die earlier than women? The latest research makes it known that the reason could be that men's hearts go into rapid decline when they reach middle age. The largest study of the effects of ageing on the heart has found that women's _ may be linked to the fact that their hearts do not lose their pumping power with age. \"We have found that the power of the male heart falls by 20-25 percent between 18 and 70 years of age,\" said the head of the study, David Goldspink of Liverpool John Moores University in the UK. \"Within the heart there are millions of cells that enable it to beat. Between the age of 20 and 70, one-third of those cells die and are not replaced in men,\" said Goldspink. \"This is part of the ageing process.\" What surprises scientists is that the female heart sees very l...\n\nQ: The text mainly talks about   _  .", "options": ["men's heart cells", "women's ageing process", "the gender difference", "hearts and long life"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1175, "question": "Rising levels of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere are a major cause of climate change, and now a new study has confirmed that atmospheric CO2is also affecting the ocean chemistry and potentially harming sea life. Montana State University scientist Robert Dore has been researching the water in the Pacific Ocean for almost two decades. We've been going to the same spot in the Pacific Ocean, and we try and characterize long-term change in the open ocean environment. And one of the key things that we measure is CO2levels. And we've been able to record this increasing quantity of atmospheric CO2into the ocean. Scientists expected that as atmospheric CO2increased, more and more of the carbon dioxide would be absorbed into the ocean, affecting the chemical balance of the sea water, with a potenti...\n\nQ: With the increase of atmospheric CO2,  _  .", "options": ["more corals will appear in the sea", "the surface water is becoming warmer", "the chemical balance of the seawater is affected", "the PH of the ocean out here has been increasing"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 124, "question": "If you go into the woods with your friends, stay with them. If you don't, you may get lost. If you do get lost, this is what you should do. Sit down and stay where you are. Don't try to find your friends -- let them find you. You can help them to find you by staying in one place. There is another way to help your friends or other people nearby to find you. Give them a signal by shouting or whistling three times. Stop. Then shout or whistle three times again. Any signal given three times is a call for help. You will be helped by others. Keep up the shouting or whistling, always three times together. When people hear you, they will know that you are not just making noise for fun. They will let you know they have heard your signal. They will give two shouts, two whistles or two gunshots. When...\n\nQ: What's the best title for the passage?", "options": ["What Do Three Shots And Two Shots Mean In A Forest", "How To Find Your Friends When You Are Lost In The Woods", "What To Do If You Get Lost In A Forest", "The Most Important Thing To Do Is To Stay In One Place"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 370, "question": "The cheetah is best known for being the world's fastest land animal, reaching speeds of just over 110kph for short period of time. However, many people know little else about this wonderful animal. The word cheetah probably comes from a Hindi word spotted animal. It is very similar to other cats but also has some obvious differences. Its body is much leaner than most cats and it has much longer legs. People sometimes make a cheetah a leopard because they both have spots, but in fact they are very different. A leopard is far heavier and more powerful, but also much slower. The cheetah's spots cover most of its body except for its stomach and throat. The cheetah's tail has spots and these become rings at the end of the tail. An adult cheetah weighs between 35-65 kilograms and is about 80 cen...\n\nQ: Many people know that the cheetah  _", "options": ["is a fast runner", "runs faster than any other animal on land", "runs as fast as it can", "is very fast for periods of time"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 30, "question": "My favourite book is The Adventure of Tom Sawyer by Mark Twain.Tom lives with his aunt Polly in a quiet street of St. Petersburg, Missouri.He's a lively and clever young boy,and he finds himself in many exciting adventures.He runs away with his two friends,Huck Finn and Joe,to an island in the middle of the Mississippi River for several days.With Huck he goes looking for treasure, with Becky he gets lost in a cave.and finally,they find a box of gold. My favourite scene in the book is when everyone thinks Tom is dead.He decides to go to his own funeral.He hides and watches for a time and then suddenly he appears. Everyone is astonished to see him but they're also pleased to see him alive. Tom is the hero of the story,but there are other important characters.Huck is an outsider and everyone ...\n\nQ: .The writer writes the article to   _  .", "options": ["ask us to read the book", "tell us how popular the book is today", "tell us when Mark Twain wrote the story", "tell us why the story sounds very real"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1489, "question": "It is the goal of politicians everywhere-----how to win and keep the trust of voters. Now researchers at the University of St Anurew's in Scotland say they may have the answer. They believe politicians could learn a lot from recent advances in science. A growing number of studies have shown that people do judge a book by its cover. Researchers say most of us make quick judgments about a person on the basis of how they look. Studies suggest that people are less likely to trust those with particularly masculine features, such as a square jaw, small eyes or a big nose. \" They are considered dominant and less trustworthy,\" says Ms Cornwell. \"It doesn't mean that men who look more masculine are less trustworthy-----it's just our first impression.\" Those with less masculine features-----larger e...\n\nQ: According to the passage, we know that   _  .", "options": ["people with good facial features must be trustworthy", "people with bad facial features could not be trustworthy", "we should judge people by their facial features", "facial features might give people some wrong impressions"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1836, "question": "Experts have put forward detailed plans for a tunnel to connect Taiwan with the Chinese mainland. The shortest proposed route would be 126 kilometers more than twice the length of the English Channel Tunnel. And the longest proposed route would be 207 kilometers. A recent conference in Xiamen, Fujian Province brought together more than 70 experts. The event was co-sponsored by universities from Taiwan and the Chinese mainland. Fujian is the province where both proposed routes would begin. There is direct passenger access between the mainland and Taiwan by air and sea at the moment. Experts say that it is better to start research sooner rather than later, although there is a lack of government funding . There are no technical problems to build a Taiwan tunnel. But it will require an improve...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true?", "options": ["Universities both at home and abroad have sponsored the plan.", "If the project is completed, the world's longest tunnel will appear.", "You can reach Taiwan from the mainland directly at present.", "The starting point of the proposed tunnel is in Fujian."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 329, "question": "Struggling in the US? Move to China! I graduated from the university with a degree of civil engineering. It is a good field but my heart was not in it. I wanted to be an actor or work in the entertainment industry...living a creative life. My choice of civil engineering was really a mistake but I realized too late. As soon as I graduated, I moved straight to Los Angeles--the home of the film and television industry! For three years, I tried to get a job in that field. I often worked as an extra in movies and TV shows--standing in the background while actors are in the foreground. This was fun for a while, but I wanted a real acting job, where I was speaking! Sadly, in Los Angeles, there is too much competition. Every race and age is represented: old, young, black, white, Asian and thousand...\n\nQ: What did the writer do before he finally decided to move to China?", "options": ["Engineer-extra-marketing-engineer", "Extra-marketing-engineer", "Engineer-extra-marketing", "Extra-engineer-marketing"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3448, "question": "Study Books Basic Study Manual Hardcover :$ 37 Future success depends on the ability to learn. Here are the answers to the questions most often asked by parents, teachers, business trainers and by students themselves. Read this book and learn: What the three barriers to study are and what to do about them. What to do if you get tired of a subject you are studying. Twenty-six simple drills to help you learn how to study easily, rapidly and with full understanding. Buy and read Basic Study Manual and use it do dramatically improve your ability to study. Study Skills for Life Hardcover: $32 L. Ron Hubbard's study technology for children opens the door to their future success by giving them the ability to study and learn. Fully illustrated (,) for easy comprehension. Learning How to Learn Hard...\n\nQ: The purpose of the passage is to   _  .", "options": ["show readers how to use the four books", "help children to learn English", "enrich students knowledge about nature", "sell the four books to students."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 713, "question": "Your Car Is Ready for Take-off The flying car has been talked about for many years,but now it appears that the idea is about to become a reality. An international company has built a two-seater plane that, at the touch of a button ,transforms into a car perfectly suitable for driving on public roads. It has been designed so that the wings fold up automatically; and it takes just 15 seconds to switch between flying and driving. With its wings fully open and the propeller spinning, it can take off from any airfield. Flying cars are quicker than traditional ones for travelling from city to city,and they can run on ordinary fuel. Another big advantage is that they are cool ,like something you would see in an action film. At the moment9however, the flying car's wheels are illegal to leave the g...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that  _  .", "options": ["few people will be able to afford a flying car", "flying cars may share the market in the future", "traffic jams will disappear because of flying cars", "driving a flying car doesn't require a pilot's license"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 347, "question": "Taichi with English narration A veteran Taichi teacher, about 38, teaches the basic 24 movements, pushinghands and self-defense techniques, suitable for the beginners and intermediate level. Time:10:00-12:00 a.m., every Sunday morning Place: Bamboo Garden Hotel, No 24, Xiaoshiqiao Hutong, jiuprefix = st1 /Gulou Street, Northwestof Drum Tower in the downtown. Fee: 60 yuan each time Chinese ink & water painting class To learn the techniques of painting a bird, flower, or lady with brushes. The Chinese philosophy and culture will also be included Time: 7:00-9:00p.m. every Wednesday Place: Library Bar, first floor, Tower B of East Gate Plaza ,right behind the poly plaza at the East Second Ring Road. Fee: 60 yuan each week Big-bowl-tea Ten yuan (US$1.2) for a cup of Chinese tea and live perform...\n\nQ: Which item is the cheapest and most relaxed to spend your leisure time?", "options": ["Taichi with English narration", "Chinese ink & water painting class", "Big-bowl-tea", "Acrobatic"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 337, "question": "Water is very important to living things. Without water there can be no life on the earth. All animals and plants need water. Man also needs water. We need water to drink, to cook our food and to clean ourselves. Water is needed in offices, factories and schools. Water is needed everywhere. There is water in seas, rivers and lakes. Water is found almost everywhere. Even in the desert part of the world, there is some water in the air. You can not see or feel it when it is a part of the air. The water in the seas, rivers and lakes is a liquid, the water in the air is a gas, and we call it water vapour . Clouds are made of water. They may be made of very small drops of water. They may also be made of snow crystals . Snow crystals are very very small crystals of ice. Ice is frozen water. It is...\n\nQ: Water has three states . They are  _", "options": ["solid, liquid and gas", "solid, vapour, snow", "drops of water, blocks of ice and crystals of water", "ice, snow and air"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1142, "question": "Cole Bettles had been rejected by a number of universities when he received an e-mail from the University of California, San Diego, last month, congratulating him on his admission and inviting him to tour the campus. His mother booked a hotel in San Diego, and the 18-year-old Ojai high school senior arranged for his grandfather, uncle and other family members to meet them at the campus for lunch during the Saturday tour. \"They were like 'Oh my God, that's so awesome ', \" Bettles said. Right before he got in bed, he checked his e-mail one last time and found another message saying the school had made a mistake and his application had been denied. In fact, all 28, 000 students turned away from UC San Diego, in one of the toughest college entrance seasons on record, had received the same inco...\n\nQ: The admissions director Mae Brown did what she could to   _  .", "options": ["protect the person who made the mistake", "punish herself for the mistake", "make up for the mistake", "help the disappointed students enter the university"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3205, "question": "At an airport I overheard a father and a daughter in their last moments together. They had announced her plane's departure. Standing near the door, he said to his daughter: \"I love you. I wish you enough.\" \"Daddy, our life together has been more than enough. Your love is all I ever needed. I wish you enough too, Daddy.\" They kissed goodbye and she left. He walked over toward the window where I was seated. I tried not to _ his privacy, but he welcomed me in by asking: \"Did you ever say goodbye to someone knowing it would be forever?\" \"Yes, I have,\" I replied. \"Forgive me for asking, but why is this a forever goodbye?\" I asked. \"I am old and she lives much too far away. I have challenges ahead and the reality is that her next trip back will be for my funeral. \" \"When you were saying goodbye ...\n\nQ: What's the most probable title of the passage?", "options": ["a talk between two men", "an interview", "your attitude to your life", "I wish you enough"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2404, "question": "Another of President Bush's critics on climate change and his former rival for the White House, Al Gore, is inprefix = st1 /Londonon Friday to launch an environmental project with the head of the Virgin Business Company, Richard Branson. They're announcing a multi-million dollar international prize to encourage development and research into new forms of low carbon technology. The prize will be available to anyone who can apply a successful method of removing large amounts of carbon dioxide from the atmosphere. Almost all scientists agree that we are experiencing global warming due to increased amounts of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere. Carbon dioxide is released when fuel is burned. Oil, coal and wood are all fuels that release the gas. When biological wasted breaks down, it also release...\n\nQ: Carbon dioxide will be produced when_.", "options": ["we are experiencing global warming.", "fossil fuel is burned", "biological waste is thrown away.", "gas is released"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1131, "question": "We are not rich by what we possess but rather by what we can do without. ----Immauel Kant Many times my friend June would say, \"If I ever get rich, I'm getting a completely new wardrobe and moving into a bigger apartment.\" I thought of her words and her chances of being rich are about as good as mine. But, to everyone's surprise, a few years ago June did come to large inheritance . At first June said very little about the money. As the initial shock disappeared, she became excited, June is a great believer in making lists, so I was surprised to find her writing down all the ways she would spend her new wealth. As time went on, she started revising the list. What had been midway down the list was now at the top. At last, I said to her, \"You know, it isn't necessary to spend all your inherit...\n\nQ: When making a list of how to deal with her inheritance, June  _  .", "options": ["didn't change it at all", "had a quarrel with the writer", "kept it secret from the writer", "made some changes to it"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2415, "question": "John and Booby joined a wholesale company together just after graduation from college the same year. Both worked very hard. After several years, however, the boss promoted Bobby to the position of manager but John remained an ordinary employee . John could not take it any more, so he sent his resignation and complained that the boss did not value hard working workers but only promoted those who said good words of him. The boss knew that John worked very hard for the years. He thought for a moment and said, \"Thank you for telling me, but I have a request. I hope you will do one more thing for our company before you leave. Perhaps you will change your mind and take back your resignation.\" John agreed. The boss asked him to go and find out anyone selling watermelons in the market. John went a...\n\nQ: The boss asked John to find out where watermelons were sold in order to   _  .", "options": ["persuade him to stay in the company", "prove he was a hardworking worker", "buy some watermelons for the company", "prove his abilities at work for himself"], "answer": 3}]